export const questions = [
    {
        id: '1',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'family',
        taxon: 'Apiaceae',
        statement: 'A distinctive feature of the Parsely family is compund terminal umbels.',
        question: 'How would you describe this type of inflorescence?',
        answer: 'Having a number of short flower stalks (pedicels), of more or less equal length, which spread from a common point, somewhat like umbrella ribs.',
        answers: [
            'Having flowers that do not have a pedicel.',
            'Having flowers growing in such a fashion that the outermost are borne on longer pedicels than the innermost.',
            'Having flowers where the oldest (and largest) are located at the top or centre.'
        ]
    },    
    {
        id: '2',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'family',
        taxon: 'Apiaceae',
        statement: 'Companion planting is the placement of different crops in proximity to the benefit of one or both plants.',
        question: 'How do species in the parsley family typically act as companions?',
        answer: 'Their the tiny flowers clustered into umbels produce nectar which attracts insects that prey on the pests of neighbouring plants.',
        answers: [
            'Provide nitrogen compounds to other plants such as grasses by fixing nitrogen from the air with symbiotic bacteria in their root nodules.',
            'Attract pests away from neighbouring plants.',
            'Act as decoys to attract flying pests away from other plants.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '3',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'family',
        taxon: 'Lamiaceae',
        statement: 'Members of the mint family share several characteristics.',
        question: 'Which quick ID is a good fit?',
        answer: 'Square stems, opposite leaves, usually aromatic.',
        answers: [
            'Square stems, alternate leaves, usually aromatic.',
            'Hollow stems, opposite leaves, usually aromatic.',
            'Hollow stems, alternate leaves, usually aromatic.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '4',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'family',
        taxon: 'Lamiaceae',
        statement: 'Members of the mint family have charcteristic flowers.',
        question: 'Which description best matches their appearance?',
        answer: 'Bilaterally symmetrical with five united petals and five united sepals.',
        answers: [
            'Bilaterally symmetrical with four united petals and four united sepals.',
            'Radial symmetrical with four united petals and four united sepals.',
            'Radial symmetrical with five united petals and five united sepals.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '5',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'family',
        taxon: 'Lamiaceae',
        statement: 'Flowers of species in the mint family are bisexual.',
        question: 'In this case what does bisexual mean?',
        answer: 'Bearing flowers which all have both male and female structures.',
        answers: [
            'Bearing separate flowers of both sexes at the same time.',
            'Bearing flowers of one sex at one time (consecutively).',
            'Bearing male, female, and bisexual flowers on the same plant.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '6',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'family',
        taxon: 'Lamiaceae',
        statement: 'Flowers of species in the mint family typically have petals fused into an upper lip and a lower lip.',
        question: 'How many of these petals do they have?',
        answer  : '5',
        answers: [
            '3',
            '4',
            '6'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '7',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Artemisia dracunculus',
        statement: 'French tarragon seldom produces any flowers (or seeds) but propagates from storage organs.',
        question: 'Which type of storage organ does Tarragon possess?',
        answer  : 'Rhizome',
        answers: [
            'Bulb',
            'Corm',
            'Tuber'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '7',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'family',
        taxon: 'Asteraceae',
        statement: 'A distingushing feature of the Asteraceae is the composite flower head.',
        question: 'What is the composition of this \'flower?\'',
        answer  : 'Disc flowers, ray flowers, or both.',
        answers: [
            'Disc flowers, ray flowers, or neither.',
            'Disc flowers, bracts, or both.',
            'Ray flowers, bracts, or neither.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '8',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Grifola frondosa',
        statement: 'Hen of the woods is weakly parasitic on several living hardwoods, and is saprobic on decaying wood.',
        question: 'At the base of which tree is it most commonly found?',
        answer  : 'Oak',
        answers: [
            'Beech',
            'Elm',
            'Maple'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '9',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Grifola frondosa',
        statement: 'The latin name for Hen of the woods is Grifola frondosa.',
        question: 'What does the epithet frondosa mean?',
        answer  : 'Full of leaves',
        answers: [
            'From the garden',
            'Hairy',
            'On walls'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '10',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Laetiporus sulphureus',
        statement: 'Chicken Of The Woods is a polyore.',
        question: 'What word cab be used to describe the fruiting body of a polypore?',
        answer  : 'Conk',
        answers: [
            'Pileus',
            'Cap',
            'Conker'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '11',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Laetiporus sulphureus',
        statement: 'Chicken Of The Woods is a parasitic and saprobic in its ecology.',
        question: 'Which description best fits where it might be found.',
        answer  : 'Growing in shelves at the base of an oak tree.',
        answers: [
            'Growing singly from moss.',
            'Growing away from the base of an oak tree in a rosette of individual caps.',
            'Growing in a clump directly from the ground.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '12',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'aves',
        rank: 'order',
        taxon: 'Passeriformes',
        statement: 'Passerines are distinguished from other orders of birds by the arrangement of their toes.',
        question: 'Which description describes this arrangement?',
        answer  : '3 toes pointing forward and one back (anisodactyly).',
        answers: [
            '2 toes facing forward (digits 2 and 3) and 2 back (zygodactyly).',
            'All 4 toes point forward (pamprodactyly).',
            '3 toes all of which point forward (tridactyly).'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '13',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Daucus carota',
        statement: 'Named in N America for it\'s similarity to lace.',
        question: 'To which queen of England is this lace attributed?',
        answer  : 'Anne',
        answers: [
            'Elizabeth',
            'Mary',
            'Victoria'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '14',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Hydnum repandum',
        statement: 'The ecology of hedgehog mushroom is mycorrhizal.',
        question: 'How is the ecology of this fungus manifest?',
        answer  : 'Colonises roots of a vascular host plant in a (generally) mutualistic relationship.',
        answers: [
            'Lives off decayed organic matter',
            'Lives off a living host.',
            'Has symbiotic relationship with roots of various plant species (without penetrating hostâ€™s cell walls).'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '15',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Craterellus tubaeformis',
        statement: 'Chanterelle and trumpet mushrooms have a distinctive spore-bearing surface.',
        question: 'Which of these appear on that surface?',
        answer  : 'False gills',
        answers: [
            'Gleba',
            'Gills',
            'Pores'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '16',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Calvatia gigantea',
        statement: 'Puffballs have a distinctive fruitbody.',
        question: 'How would you recognise a puffball?',
        answer  : 'It\'s brown, dust-like spores are emitted when the mature fruitbody bursts or is impacted.',
        answers: [
            'It has an open cap with spore-bearing gills.',
            'The spores develop internally in the gleba and are exposed in the form of a foul-smelling gel.',
            'Spores form on a spongy mass of downward-pointing tubes.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '17',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'fungi',
        rank: 'species',
        taxon: 'Calvatia gigantea',
        statement: 'Puffballs have a distinctive fruitbody.',
        question: 'How would you recognise a puffball?',
        answer  : 'It\'s brown, dust-like spores are emitted when the mature fruitbody bursts or is impacted.',
        answers: [
            'It has an open cap with spore-bearing gills.',
            'The spores develop internally in the gleba and are exposed in the form of a foul-smelling gel.',
            'Spores form on a spongy mass of downward-pointing tubes.'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '18',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'insecta',
        rank: 'genus',
        taxon: 'Bombus',
        statement: 'Bumblebees form colonies with a single queen.',
        question: 'How many individuals would typically be found in a nest?',
        answer  : '50',
        answers: [
            '250',
            '1000',
            '5000'
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '19',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'insecta',
        rank: 'genus',
        taxon: 'Bombus',
        statement: 'Different species of bumblebee in a region often resemble each other in a mutually protective way.',
        question: 'What name has been given to this natural phenomenon?',
        answer  : 'MÃ¼llerian mimicry',
        answers: [
            'Batesian mimicry',
            'Mertensian mimicry',
            'Wasmannian mimicry',
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '20',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'insecta',
        rank: 'genus',
        taxon: 'Bombus',
        statement: 'Bumblebees have aposematic (warning) coloration, often consisting of contrasting bands of colour.',
        question: 'What purpose does this serve?',
        answer  : 'Beneficial to both predator and prey, since both avoid potential harm.',
        answers: [
            'Beneficial to both potential predators since they avoid potential harm.',
            'Beneficial to the bumblee since it avoids potential harm.',
            'Benefits species ressembling bumblees by warding off potential predators.',
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '21',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'insecta',
        rank: 'genus',
        taxon: 'Bombus',
        statement: 'Bumblebees have long hairy tongues.',
        question: 'How are they put to use?',
        answer  : 'Feeding and gathering nectar for their young.',
        answers: [
            'Feeding and gathering pollen for their young.',
            'For pollination in return to nectar.',
            'For pollination in return to pollen.',
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '22',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'plantae',
        rank: 'genus',
        taxon: 'Bombus',
        statement: 'Pollen grains are male microgametophytes of seed plants.',
        question: 'What are gametophytes?',
        answer  : 'One of the 2 alternating phases in the life cycle of plants and most algae.',
        answers: [
            'The diploid multicellular stage in the life cycle of a plant or alga.',
            'One of the 3 alternating phases in the life cycle of plants and most algae.',
            'A diploid multicellular organism that develops from a haploid spore.',
        ]
    },
    {
        id: '23',
        provider: 'snapdragon',
        iconicTaxon: 'insecta',
        rank: 'genus',
        taxon: 'Bombus',
        statement: 'Queen bumblebees lay one of two types of egg.',
        question: 'What do unfertilised eggs which contain chromosomes only from the queen become?',
        answer  : 'Male bees',
        answers: [
            'Male worker bees',
            'Female worker bees',
            'Queen bees',
        ]
    },

];